啦啦又没开麦克风下
午好下
午好非常
迅速的来了一个突击这样
很迅速嗯今
天
没有其他的安排然后
呃想了一下晚上
打游戏可能会没有那么好看所以
还是下午加加一点点内容吧好吧嗯听
得见那
谢
谢黄味薯条的港梦下午好吃了
吗喝了吗今天中
午点的
什么什么寿司的外卖好腻啊吃两口就吃不
下
了准备准备等到一
会儿播完了再把剩下的吃完情
愿了想吃好吃的饭
啊寿司好吃但是今天今天
今天吃这
个很腻啊坚持的很腻啊他加了那个加了
很多的酱我不
知道为什么要加那么多酱放
冰箱是肯定的谢谢三成小香豆港
们今天开始放暑
假了吗明
天开始放但今天还要收拾收拾东西
什么的明天就
开始放暑假了我们暑假之后的那
个直播安排再看到时候怎
么办吧还没有想好还没有想好怎么
一个魔法不是吃了三文鱼
寿司啊今天
吃了那个什么鳗鱼鳗鱼跟鳕
鱼的好哎是鳕鱼吗我咋记
不太清了只记住一个是
鳗鱼这个鳗鱼的好
腻
呀好腻呀一天
从早播到晚一天从
早播到晚的话可能想
不出来那么多要讲
的话就
要找东西来混一
下了没有鳕鱼寿司吗哦
这样吗就不太记得完全不
记得自己点的时候点的是什么东
西了有一个是满语声
音
好小这个
声音还好小
吗我已经加了两个分贝了等一下哦如果声
音好小
的话我再调整一下哦今天
呢讲话的音量也稍
微大了一点然后我想今天下
午是是加那
个亮哥回还是看看纪
录片还是看看纪
录片吧下午如果练歌的话感觉晚上没
有力气讲话了嗯谢谢真理路的钢蹦啊别轻
说谢谢子恒的钢
蹦又早退了吗今天
没有早退谢谢陈南的钢
棒早到下下午早下午早谢
谢
九零七五的钢棒翘课
家人跑路没有没有真的没有唉不要奶妈
妈说了哥我们
可一天播二十五小时什么对你真的很
重要不不不不不可能啊不可能
啊嗯以小松
弟的经历每天播三四
个小时是极限了
就
比这个时间再长的话剩下
的二十个小时可能都
要拿来玩手机睡觉
了还是需要
有
一些还是需要有一
些其他的这个生活安排的谢谢
安夸零四的钢棒谢谢风
霜引经进落制的钢棒想试试生的又不是三
文鱼的
话可以试试小猪夹哦没有看到这个哪里有
卖小猪夹鱼
的
店哦之前我去吃过那
个炸大猪夹鱼很好吃电台算直
播吗电台算
吧等电台的话唉其实如
果放暑假的话可以
给你们播户外电台找一个网好的地方哦昨
天有
一个下播的他找的舰长没有谢
谢谢拜
拜大王 q 的舰
长谢谢掌
位钢板还是
挺
容易的舰长谢谢大家
的支持看一下吧就是我我
需要先去测试一下那
个山上网好不好然
后找一个没有人
的地方
去去植物园或者去山
场植物园人太多了我找一个很偏然
后又没有网唉又
有网的地
方种地电台重地电台的话只有在地里面拔
草啊谢谢椰
脂
芒果西米露的港本绿色能不能收盘了
再播现在又想看又
见不得绿
色咋回事儿啊这是
在干嘛真的有
这
种地方吗会有吧去寻觅一下会有吧谢谢就
是一零一八
的嗯
钢蹦
才播了几天小棕榈已经对夸夸无感不敢想
知道
会看咋这样
什么没空空要
努力的钢蹦
放假可以娘
念七天一百六十八
小时不断炼不可能
的这种
东西
肯定不可能的谢谢四小时录天猫机
的钢蹦什么啊今天没有
去学校啊今
蹦今天要收
拾东西就没
有去学校
不要这样恶意揣测到底
小松榈是一个什么样的
学生形象
啊谢谢天才美少女神乐的
钢梦
能不能等收盘了再开播这个也
是谢谢藤泽心菜的
钢梦解说一姐下午好
下午好晚上都
能看直播了好爽啊我我
我我昨天测试完之后就很担心这个
晚上打游戏的部
分啊大家可能大家可能觉得小松弟在直
播间还挺活泼的但是呃就是有的时
候感觉人
多会有
点说说不
上话知道吗就是会担
心自己
晚上可能想不起来说什么就
就就但是但是也没有人这么多玩儿
过那就看嗯那看晚上什么样子吗你会印着
嘎嘎笑吗其
实是其实
是觉得大家又很好笑然后又不知道讲什么
然后所
以只能
一直笑谢谢莎莎痛饮长岛冰茶的港梦野彩
电
台不可以野踩哦大家不可以野踩哦只是纯
粹遛弯儿的这个电态给哪里强夫
的高们千万要穿短
袖短裤播户外肉身四虫啊在户外肯
定是肯定是要穿长裤子
的谁谁户外穿短裤啊能喂喂
蚊子蚊子有点饱了谢谢寻梅奥飞少的感冒
小松女兔学
很
开心谢谢你哎小松乐园
二零四的他应该是这位打野仙死了可以
和别人一样呃就是唉没有懂那个游
戏到底怎么玩儿就没
有懂那个游戏到底怎么玩儿可能还要
再看一下吧就是捡东
西然后搬到家里嘛但他那
个看起来我很容易迷路然后
还有还有怪什么的
然后里
面
有乌漆麻黑的大帮忙
看攻略已经看了已经看了一点点
了等到等到一会儿
再再研究
一下吧谢谢一六四哪的女的的港
冒大仗谢谢公学的港冒懂你意思
我李哼来了你不是我领
后嘛就是就大
家不会有那种集
体活动的时候感觉其他人都热
热闹闹的然后自己想往
里面说话但是想不起来说什么话然后如果
就是他们
正在说一个话题你
这个时候唐突的去说一句的话又
怕打
扰到他们就或者是跟跟别人同时
张口说话这个事情就很可怕这两个人同
时说出第一个字
然后在在讲话的这个这个这个事情就很
可怕谢谢月游的港个大方当
解说就好会会会努力的
会会会会努力看明白这个
游戏是什么样的谢谢三 HURSM 七
的港广绿
色解说大家游戏水平太好笑了所以
最好笑的应该是
最好笑的应该是小棕榈嘛谢谢香菜
一生之旅的没事在观
战士说不定可以和某前辈一
起结束不知道大家都玩过没有啊昨天晚上
因为
我们是先测试的嘛只有我和那个小鹿我们
两个是完全
没有玩过这个游戏的嗯昨天线下咋的但是
纯净了大脑还还不一定还不一
定到时候谁最去呢谢谢无
所爱的敢冒大方拔地里面的菜吧别别别别
别别
别别别别不要不要拔
别人地里的菜
拔自己家地里的菜但是小棕榈
没有地谢谢无谋大逃的刚刚
小松榈不就穿的短裤吗原来是宅
女来的对啊对啊穿这个短
裤只是因为短裤好看当然不会穿短裤出
门
了谢白雪的嗯高峰
那我知道今
晚的什么这是什
么山羊吗是
谁的好吧你学会了
高高大方冷暴
力会努力想话说的但是如果
真的想不出来话的话大家大大方方笑吧就
是可以
尽情嘲笑啊谢谢李四
郎的钢棒联动只要开
怀大笑就行再再说
吧再说吧啊天哪把这段纲温
念完我们就去看那个
纪录
片谢谢四颗三猫的高梦小松你别怕
今天我们会赢的会吗会吗好
像大家只要大家
一起赢了小松弟就不
会就是呃就是被抛弃
掉吧然
后昨天
有听他们讲说好像
最后如果扣不呃凑不够钱
的话可以卖尸体可以把小棕驴
卖掉哎呀很便宜的小苏
榈的尸体卖掉也算做出
一些贡献了谢谢宫学的蔬
叉那我本该直播完
犊空气谢谢
安利博瑞
的官
帮进游戏很快就
可能不在一个语音频道
我我会我会找其他人就是
死死跟
着的就是跟在他后面吧就
起到
一个搬运工的作用目前的计
划是这
样的但是真的晚上玩起来跟这个
计划有没有关系就还不
好说呢谢谢护理部部长的钢棒什么说什
么鼓励鼓励你
们那要加油生活总会继续
为什
么要为什么要念这个加油加油现
在穷的能搞吗非要玩的
好才行我玩的好
像但是你死的太快的话其
实是没有办法玩那么好笑的猪那
个测试的时候测试的时候我一不
小心就是一脚踩空了就
摔下去摔死了啪就
死掉了谢谢小天使的
就叉子咋那么可爱做什么
都是对的别别别别别
别别别别别别别别别别别别别别感觉有太
肯
肯定打游戏戏
的话还是需要一些压力
啊我觉得打游戏呃压力比
别人和被
压力力很重要
要的一部分如果当事人不太介意的
话而且会有那种
很吃压力的人但小
兄莉这种知
道自己屈的时候就可
以随便压力就你没
有办法压力
到一条蛆你们就算压
力我也知道
啊就是这样啊那那那咋了那
给你们打过预防
针了谢谢超级
海狸猫的钢梦千万别
戴面具咬死
队友还有这种功
能啊没着急啊我去看一下谢谢嗯亚尼啊克
劳迪尔的钢
梦
十个人玩很简单不会玩大方摸鱼划水就
行已经跟大家说过了就是会摸鱼划水啊小
松的瑞斯是
不是
五毛一斤得卖多少次不敢
想了昨天没有遇到面具的部分
我再去研究研究我再去看一下那种有没有
那种意
图流攻略谢谢逍售哥今天吃
什么干猫如果联动一开始
的话就鬼叫
蒙混过关吧
冷静的河水中那人多了会
担心
鬼叫吵到大家这都都
还挺吵的谢谢三
仔的钢蹦
给小棕榈出门就
死也太可
爱不可爱谢
谢做
末
也要吃
铜烧的钢蹦怎么又开始又有谁忍心
责怪的责怪吧尽管责怪吧谢
珠光嗯到刚刚大大方
方一起当二路解说这
个要看打游戏之后是什么样啊谢谢 TR
户
外 QS 的钢
崩准备黑天鹅什么时候开
看就是准备开看了
不准再发港货了我们要看看纪录片了谢谢
柔
老的
钢蹦粘
住白色好吗会的会会
死死粘着请放心感觉他很
擅长玩游戏的样子谢
谢正逢夏末秋
凉的钢蹦呃室外找蜂窝特别值钱
没有看到过蜂窝
之前
没有看到过蜂窝谢谢优卡是雪人
的送杀的 DYS 以前
播这
个效果很好有有兴趣可
以观摩一下就打算等会儿下播了去看一
下就是其他
人大概是
怎么玩的对学习一些基础操作吧哎梁
梦成英呢刚我没事那几个前辈都
停潮了除了看看前大家都好可爱呀啊昨天
晚上语
音的时候感觉大
家都好可爱呀来看
视频吧哎哎哎错了错了怎
么点
到开播设置了哎又漏后台了
不好意思哦不好意
思哦你
帮忙开播嗯这跟摄像头没有关
系这
是开播跟摄像头没有关
系收打看吧到第四集了哎
呦我去为什么声
音又这么大 imagine a
world o
ne
by females
as a genetic
testing gr
ound 哦就没有
中文了 a world wear
miles
are merely a
breeding
experiment and
where females can
pick
the best genes
to pass on to
their you
ng by founmings or
fare in nature 不
知道啊 this world
exists 那
我可能需要再
挡一下这个标啊等一下
哦应
该是只有前
前几集是
这个有中文的后两集
就没有了那我可能还需要挡一
下
另外一个表等我再找
一个太努力了黑天敏有
点可怜了黑
天明就
看看小松榈叫吧老师能老师能
翻
译一下吗老
师跟不上 the
battle of the
sexis is
a war without amy
tecti
on between
males and females
it pe
rsists in almost
every
species
on earth 嗯 at
its hard is a
raging c
onflict females
want
to choose their
mate
miles want ants to
make
sure that
chose en
但我感觉这个画质是我
那天看看的时候戴滤镜吗我
感
觉更复古 females
forever
traml why i was a
beari
ng mextro miles 感
觉更糊了只有四百八呀他放冰冰给我四百
八在 ca
n be
downright dirty
when it
comes to sex
females can be
ruthless
there in 今天打开的是这个
视频吗是
这个啊我是说前四集是有中文的后两
集没有 is as far as
they are concerned
male
s can come and go
我就对了
getting hold at
the right white
stuff i
s crucial to many
femal
es strategy
for sexual sucess
cess
the females
through the
ir
paces and beyond
even o
rgasm isnt the
end of
it they
have the sperms
turn fo
r a rough ride
they hav
e to
navigate pal 但是他
就是哎他他他是英文我就不太好我
就不太好念 which can 能
太
好念是个什么内
容 genitors are far
from
a lock
and key
arrangement the
female
reproductive tr
ack is
a torture a
substical p
ath which can be
an 打读吗
不敢 sperm 真的真的朗诵
了就就万一真
吃红外 c 了怎么办感觉
管的还还挺
严的你摁错了会
举万别吧 to a female
spam i
s
a foreign body 大家是
什么 wo
rking three
朗诵只练习一下这个英语听力了小棕榈看
不
懂什么一只眼
睛看字幕一只眼睛看 IA
female sex
ual
choice 看到 no
shappe
not only the
sexual beh
avior of many
miles but theyre
sexua
l biology
too 这个地
方当时昆虫挺多的 to be
wanted o
nly for your body
might
sound like
a milal fantasy 我看
到很
多很多那个前面有
蜘蛛啊还有螳螂有 six
lave to these fan
fatil
e
can mean paying
the hea
viest of tols take
one
of the most
extreme
environments on
earth the
north pole
producing yo
ung with any
chance of survival
here
needs ds
fafather with the
very
best genes
on offer one one
ll fi
ght to prove it
能念吗不能念好
像小时
候有见过那种南
极北极
的纪录片是北极
熊 and still
hamperature
s 的内容还挺好玩的 theres
just one problem
findin
g a hot date to
lose
it with 应应
配繁体字幕我
觉得繁体字幕可能
就是脑子没
有办法这个抓那么快谁的发北极熊捕食企
鹅
tees over seventy
kilo
meters away when
it com
es to sex female
polar
bears lie back
relax 哎从
这个角度看的话北极熊没有那么白哎还是
just
like the suck come
and
get me clue 脏脏的我就出
演了
一个人 to a lasty
milopoo
air it must be the
swee
ter
smell on her 还是动画片
里面的是是
白的
polar bears have a
very slow breeding
rate
one now maonly
coming
into season about
once
every 北
极熊皮肤是黑色的北极熊
的那个鼻子是黑色的所以
他后面的皮肤也都是偏深
色
的 may not get many
oppo
rtunities
to have sex
in his lifetime
想起来那个了那个斑马到底是
hell go to 长黑毛的白马
还
是长白毛的黑马 his quest
start
s with
AA ruwling days
walk he
travels thirty
kilomet
ers that is losing
weig
ht driven by one
urge o
nly but hes
about to need all
his e
nergy hes on a
collisi
on course with
another
eager suter 长黑白毛的应
该是
皮肤是棕色的吧然后有黑白色的毛
nine hu
ndred kilograms of
musc
le
tear into each
other 谢谢
港
梦最不压抑的直播
间啊没有这种说法
谢
谢神影嗯我色哒哒的我刚报北京没
野人帮
他们洗澡命我了 the ice
main th
eyre fighting
over ido
ls
in the snow 请放心啊不
会点到其他的界面 back at
the ba
ckground the
smaller er
has been sent
packing
the
only thing hell
be lo
oking today his
wings
the nine year old
taken
a battering but
sex dr
ive
him on across more
and
norw frozen ice
plannin
g forward without
food
不不吃不喝吗吃不喝还是有点过分了
even a coach 吃吃吃饭了
吗 cmb
bering onto
land hes near
exhausti
on but once again
he pi
cks up the subttle
smil
e in the snow in
fact i
ts getting
stronger an
d
stronger and
stronger 唉
之前其实
还有好奇过像这种大
型野生动物的行为到底是怎么拍
摄的好像企鹅有放那
种鸟形状的摄像头混在
企鹅群里面拍的但不知道北极熊
要怎么拍啊北极熊
是人在很远处拍吗控制住
谁假请哦所以还有那种假的那个企鹅
蛋什么的有伪装
上镜的纪
录
片对对对对对 female
polar bears 去看绿
色星球
的时候有这
个是绿色
精彩吗那
个幕后怎么怕开的
问题 but it
could take two
weeks 人在
近处拍
会无视但
是看起来会很危
险啊毕竟还是野
生动
物 a bone rights in
the
middle
of of is painis it
s ca
lled a baculum and
it d
oesnt just help
to stimulate
population
it keeps him hard
howe
ver
tired is 富贵险出江山
but it
was why he doesnt
need
by agram hes
about
to pay a halish
price s
ex
is so violent
而且感觉不知道是因
为有
一些题材之前大
家
都已经这个拍过了然
后这两年就没有没有想起来特别好玩的纪
录片
找的时候也没找到 he limps
away
spent and broken
she
is got on she
wanted a
fertilized bag but
although she made
littl
e effort before or
duri
ng sex now she
invested
everything in her
unbow
and the first
thing sh
e does is
put the baby to be
on i
nobody freezes the
embr
yos development
bia met
hod could delayed
in pl
antation 还有还有冷
冻 fferllized eggs
stops
growing and lies
reflo
ating 哦
the former 懂了懂
了 this mother
needs tim
e to prepare to be
a si
ngle parent
she starts a
friendzy t
o get quick fast 下
次可以看大侦探吗嗯下次
的纪录片还没
选好下次再来看吧我们
把这个看完一下就选一
个呃和动物无关的嗯
全念别的领域的小海豹哦到
那个北极熊
吃海豹 eight months
later
proof that
this frienrenzy of
feed
ing
fighting
and forunicating
was wo
rth it finally
arrives
还
是小的萌去好小一个 still
become and out
back org
goes horribly
wrong for a sex
mad of a susupal
we see
a real fan for
tile de
liver the love
bike
from hell and we
expose
the toxy turv sex
secr
et 能直
播看猫和老鼠吗其实可以申请看猫和老鼠
ever
ybody decomposers
in th
e
australian boook a
post
mortem which show
this
little
malsupil 那置 with
the ho
rrendous
end 有道理
不吃饭哦好了准
备玻璃 he was played
with
open source aneia
in
test
analysis 有代林现在
是不是只有那个澳洲有分布了
his whole 之
前叫什么 collapse 袋鼠带狼
袋袋熊吗是袋熊吗
好
像就是有带
类哦
his fammiles six
and
anto kindness 你怎么你
妈这不是很
极
限啊爱无嗯 but now hes
in a sexual frenzy
hes
eleven month sold
rich
班长班是早就灭绝了吗
灭绝了呢他也是
那个内片的呀美周也有
the copylight 啊懂了
but i
t would kill him 蜜
袋
his disdoster and
level
s are rising
dangersly
high 但大家
一般想起来的话还是
会就是
对澳洲的印象会深一点 so 起
源
于南美南美的动物
植物倒是没
怎么了解呢 antikinda
sex is
far and tender its
sava
ge males
bites and claw
females
kick roll and
his 你们不要再
打了 hes equiit for
the
job 不
要再打了 testiacles
are muc
h larger another
mossipiilals his
size i
t can take gets
well of
our sex
session before the
sper
m does its
job 你
为什么打架
不知道可能他们就是是这样的
but even
after this
marathon bel
matmeeting
the authorio is
being s
atisfied its
straight
back to business
search
ing for more
sex and more sex
and mo
re cant 幸好这个 he
just ke
eps on
coming and going 幸
好这个画质
还
是比较模糊的
再高清一
点真的很担心被 bban
掉了 stress homone
strip
又
一个不吃饭的刚那个也不吃
饭啊 gging
the complete break
他那个也
不吃饭这个
也算是 is in death
word wi
th sperm and is
not
alone every mile
who
makes its the
same 不是那
个 but
why are they quite
stie
nce for sex
many females
die while winning
so th
e
more females a
male has
sex with the
greater t
he
chance at least
one wil
l survive to raise
his
young
and theres
another twi
st if the males
live to
see a second
season th
eres the
possibility they
might
mate with their
own dau
ghters maybe its
natur
es way of
stopping in
breeding 你要
是这么
去理解的话好
像也
有点道理 in the
ventikindne
ss
but it wipes out
an ent
ire generation of
males
although some
creatures
make the
ultimate sacrifice
to p
roduce offspring
other species have
seck
s
on tap without
riisking
death from the job
哦 i
f ever theres a
role r
eversal of
stereotypica
l male and
female sex drive
this i
s it all across
the
tropics some nimbo
bird
s are also having
an or
gy this
is swinging
jakanostyle
and its the
luckladies who are
set
on
me 水鸟的水鸟的那个大脚就很好了
its knoon stop
set 腿也很
长脚也很
大仔细去观察的话那感觉还挺萌
的 but although
theyre
only half the size
of t
heir partners they
re g
ot more than
twice the work to
do ja
canas arent like
most
birds enabled its
a ma
ns work which has
never done 和小
鸟一样的 have to
provide
a lot more than
sperm t
hey left home
alone to
build and defend
nests
blue tax and raise
thei
r cheeks 之前
有见过某
种殃机的小鸟那个
那个就那鸟很
小然后脚很大就很萌欢迎
sometimes t
heyll have
sex with four
miles 给能奶
吗 but
theres more to
neighbo
rhood
then swingming
marsh bi
rds creditors are
every
where and up
the first sight of
dang
er this fearless
father
阮志
伟 however this is
cunni
ng not caroudist 扭
头就跑 at a safe
distance
from his chicks
he flippps out it
s a w
ell rehearsed
drink the
broken
wing is he now
looks sm
all defenseless
and a
very easy target 这
个好厉害
but once
hes distracted
the dan
ger away from the
nest
dad turns on his
hills
and heads
back to his pad 没完
moth
er is busy with a
neighbor in a
single se
ason she may
have as many as
thirty
partners this
environme
nt
demands such
action 是
an against only a
quart
er of how egs will
actually hach and
of th
ese only about
sixty pe
rcent of the
chicks 不是
five 对于鸟
类来说这个比例涵挺高
的我感觉我感觉咬
了一道好啊蛋啊
就会因为很多原因孵不
出来 no time for any
othe
r responsibility 受
天气影响了
也
很大 the genes
for the female
jcanns
endless pursuit of
sex
有见
过那个白头背的鸟
窝就会因为大暴雨然后
那个
and 觉那个鸟
的那个妈妈没有回来吗所以那
个潮最后就弃掉了 by
what seems to be 还
有就是
小鸟已经孵出来了之后不会因
为下大雨然
后室温之
类的 welcome to the
twili
ght world of make
it
more right
cooperated t
he worlds
strangers
underground
sex factory 头上如
个也没孵出 their
business ma
king babies
competition
is
tough and the
bus is a force
of
nature a female
never t
o be argugely 这
个没毛的感觉
就有点吓人
还是喜欢毛茸茸的小动
物 one hundred
positions
available in her
facto
ry applicants must
be
tiny bold
and look like a
freszle
d hot dog and it
helps
to be related to
the bo
ss for this
is a family
business and in
her com
pany sons 刚刚那个是不是灌
水质不
是水质啊它翻译
出问题
是很正常的 she
has a hurry ine of
appr
oximately three
sons
who are required
to sup
ply spam whenever
not a
sense on 啊
shes very
demanding 哎 this
queen
is a non stopped
movean
t making machine 喝
口水 new letters of
twelv
e
to thirty seven
pumps a
rrive every eighty
days
八
十天嗯声音一台那他是不是存
活率比较低呀 young for a
mont
h they
start eating
solids aft
er two weeks and
its quite
literally a
crap diet they
feed on
the workers fees
bad t
hat it may sound
the ba
by
more res faces is
organ
ic predigested
superfoo
d assce of
nutrition an
d bacteria to
protect t
heir stomachs
the remaining
members o
f the colony are
kept b
usy finding food
mainta
ining the home
defending the
borough 很
tunneling but they
have no time for
sex 啊
they
never get the
chance to
spread their gene
beca
use their
queen has
decreated she
keeps the workers
sex
ual instincts at
bay wi
th a theromon in
eurine
it
seeps throughout 这
个倒
是没有看过其他的
这个纪录片讲
过唉之前没有看过 the
workers do
nt just
relationant
they wall over it
the q
ueens theremoone
suppr
esses female
sexual moe
s
male testos
sterone and
spun letls 粪里有益的
细菌能活过胃香动
物应该没有那么强劲的胃我记得 and
they
contribute more to
the future of moal
at k
ind by helping the
quee
n care
for her offspring
人的
胃酸人的胃是很强大的可
以消化掉很多东西但其他动物好像就是没
有那么
强大 choice
of
home helps this
social
system work the
maize o
f tunnels is a
safe hav
en they are left
alone
to live
breed and expand
their
bizarre bread
family
business
when youre after
sex
picking the right
time
to make your move
be cr
ucial particularly
啊
到关头啊
perfections 好帅
this fem
ale is one
of the deadliest
states
in the world
不救平常的嘛这个都不知
道具体什么动物是
什么样子的 and not just
food
经
典演员这个三角头看起来就
很帅 theres no such
thin
g as safe
thanks for a male
pragm
antis 小时候
看黑猫警常吓的吓哭
了黑猫警警长呢动
物习象哎都显得都是一些比较有
意思的
my romantics often
moun
t females from
behind h
ere they should be
safe
from grasping legs
bog
hts or worse
in
theory 小时候看那种故
事书也
喜欢讲螳
螂 trying to
see
i to eye
with these
females can be
very
risky mtated our
visual
predators and
often ea
t anything that
moves s
o
this males
approach cou
ldnt be more
cautious
hes taking things
slow
ly very
slowly he moves no
fast
er than half a
centomme
ter he gets closer
and
closer and closer
until
hes almost face
to fa
ce
我螳螂能
不能算是某种意义
上的病娇感觉不算哎
so far so good pp
can s
ee what what
intententi
ons are so he
takes the
plunge and makes
it on
that she seems
to have other
ideas 啊这时
候
for play she gives
him
a love bite and it
s th
e worst one
imaginable
she starts doit is
咋这样
if she wanted a
blind d
ate shes
走了吗时时开始
嚼嚼嚼
了了 but not mant it
far
from it
instinctively h
e
manages to flip
whats
left of
his body back on
top of
her and he manages
to
get down to
business he
s completely lost
his mind 小时候看这集
黑猫警长被吓晕了你看这个
实拍更吓人 its
have nerve centres
loca
ted in
various pounds of
their
bodies 哎分开
控制是吧 it he
loses his
innobitions o
h his genitors
take cha
rge and he has sex
like
theres no
tomorrow he
continues to
thrust un
til the last drop
of semon has been
squee
zed from his
remains
as he woners his
away s
pent empty and
decapita
ted at least these
given his unborn
childr
en ahead start his
the
female
cleans itself up
shes
had sex
and supper a
nutritious
meal to sustain
her an
d helpare off
spring 就
分了子涵 the dates a
been a
need success
still to come
customers
calls chaos at an
open air sexshow 昆
虫有
很多分布是神经节所
以就说有那种 and the
hard fac
ts why othe
businesses
on a crash
collision cr
ews 去掉头身体还能动吗像像
螳螂这样
even
good old fashion
cool s
hip can be a
kilenup in
an
indian grassland
its b
aking hot and
getting h
otter by the
minute but its
not jus
t the sun
lets getting
these for
these
heart and baby
their th
irsty 这
个这个滤镜好
搞笑我带着一只
在身体 theyre
waiting for
show times 谢谢
呃那外龙都留记得港
梦螳螂这个是经
典
谣言吃饱环境压力不大的时候三
分之二熊螳螂能全
身而退这样子
吗那可能就是之前的纪录片喜欢
拍这种谢谢好像是快为
阿信的刚刚舞头公和美美
吃
尸体这个不是这个
没
有吃尸体
啊
这个不是
直接开吃吗谢谢小赚
五花棒棒棒对自然失望啊谢谢秋雨独孤
的钢蹦对澳
洲的印象是或者往
前背 but if it
doesnt 对澳洲的印象
全部是有大类动物 late
cameras h
ave to run a
goldvit to
try and find a
pitch a
ll this
temperatures ap
proach 二十多 degrees
what
could be worth
this tor
ture the opposite
sex i
n a nearby meadow
a gro
up of shoganals
are get
ting ready
heard a female
blackbox
theyre about to
come
into season and
will soon be
looking fo
r misr right but
theyr
e very choesy 我不是
these
females have
the luxury of
grazing d
rinking what
they want and
taking
shelter from the
heat 真
奈好大吃大喝
中 hello mayo tries
a di
fferent approach
and he
ad
straight into the
group
but these
females are
looking for
a mile who can 如果
头上顶这种脚的话会
不会跑步的时候我感觉头沉沉
的有
点
跑不动了 theyre
gearing up
for short time 你
个头会比身子重一马
刀现在头又冲出去了 and this
audience wont be
hard
to impress as the
siren
s arrive they
check out
the ground then
stop very time 保持平
衡的话但你
跑起来的时候跑
起来
的时候因为头很沉
然后那个头就会惯性很大
就会往前冲 and hope 这实心
的也
很沉 but these
females 我那
个荷
包蛋子对 the biggest
the strongest they
re
ararchfor susuper
lug f
ight break help
有的物种
就是因为脚太大被灭绝了行动不方便嘛掏
钱
跑的更快哦 a mile
choice is
chances but this
female
doesnt like what
she
smells finally
in the center of
the fi
eld the best seat
in th
e house she
finds the male she
了感觉这
个 wand shes about
to d
rive
这个雄性一直都
是一个仰着头的
状况啊 she
teases intense in
but s
he doesnt let him
get
too close not yet
is
frantic fletting
can la
st
up to an hour so
maybe
its no surprise 哎
是啊吗那叫
高梦有一次
配螳螂
之前乱喂呢
我
放到一起还没配上弓那一
跑他就被咬下来 oh no 是不是
of th
e shows over for
him su
ch females
want their males
to pro
ve that theyre
the
best equip to far
ther
young 人头是羊头可能
是为了减轻颈
椎的压力有可能确实
是他这
个脚有点太大了感
觉站到整个身子的一半了 but
the siz
e
matter to all
females 啊
当蜘蛛了
是吗 man of the
south
american forest
floor t
he maalga lia
tranantua
a
huge and deadly
predato
r hes got
the fans to kill
the
popoison paralyse
but w
hen being hard
really c
ounts hes a softy
这种恐怖吗
就就是大如果果得得
这种怖
是是会觉得只是看到就
觉得
很恐怖还是是是
觉得他长得丑的那种恐怖还是对这
个嗯动物有一
些刻板印象的偏
见所以觉得
很恐怖看到就发毛就觉得得长得丑
是吗 after his 他被
咬他被咬的话看纪
录片倒不至于吧 in the
familiar equipment
for
the job hows you
going
to manage it 多毛又多足
啊
unlike most
spiters 谢
谢不叫呜呜的刚刚
他有阳刚
之气阳光是现在哪
里 get their own
sperm
this
lean to sheet
of silk will act
as a serm spunge
cruell
ing under his west
he p
represses his
testicles up
against th
e threads
and the jacket
lakes he
then craells to
the top and sucks
up hi
s
semon
surrangge
like a pandagis
called
petty 哦这个好
像这个好像是之前我在科普书里面看过
now carrying his
own fr
esh seed
he sets off on his
firs
t date what female
coul
d resist such
a gift this one 谁走
的 and
shes deadly shes
sen
t mark the silk
in her borough gh
with
theromones and
sure eno
ugh they work she
s
winding him in but
what
four torantulous
have
very weak highle 眼
睛不
好用 the has on her
body
vibraate as the
approac
hes
but not
necessarily bec
ause shes
sexually exciiting
中配那么
有意思
中配还是配的
阴扬顿
挫但其实内容是差不
多的为什么不把六
级全部做成中配呢 she sees
is th
e initiative but
does
she want to greet
him o
r greet him its
still
isnt clear he has
back
up all mating
books on
his front legs ks
if he
s lucky theyll
help h
im push her body
into the right
position
to have sex
if hes not their
prime
to grab her phans
插入 ho
pefully 插入
此中毒牙这
这个时候还
要还有两个人对着咬
吗别怕 during her but
ther
es
no guarantee he
needs t
o push
her body up and
deliver
his
gift as quickly
uncarefully as
possible 谢谢钻谢
谢谢的黄棒如仔细
听的话又有很多阴阳的地
方字幕又没翻译出来根本没仔细
听帮我
仔细听一下 releases his
sper
m from the bulls
its
the most unlikely
orgas
m and as soon as
its o
ver is of around
fifty
percent of miles
are
killed by their
partner
s either during or
afte
r thanks 嗯这个怎么也被杀掉
了 thi
s for tele heads
back t
o her borough
思云 shall have
young tog
ether 吃
饱了就不会吃雄
性了但会攻
击因为他
就算不会吃点也也攻击呀
啊那个像
个螳
螂一样 two
or three more
times but
shortly after
that 有道理 female
oranang
elers
can eat their
mates but
at least they
stand
a chance to escape
可以可
以开着跑路了 lurking
on the sea beed is
livi
ng proof of just
how
powerful and
evolutiona
ry force females
can be
这是什
么这个没见过 someone who
s go
t her males just
where
she
wants them beneath
the
waves
of the
mediterranian th
is females having
sex n
ot with one
mile but with up
to twenty 这个是什么 at
the
same time and
we cant see
any of them this
is a f
emale bennana a
one her
bodies only
the size ze a
mobile ph
one but her her
rosses
can
grow to over a
meter
in length 啊 used
for fe
eding 是 hows it
her 啊这
个是嘴啊 passts a
bizarre acal spell
besi
de
her are her
fertinized
eggs but when they
hatc
h their sex
is undecided any
larvy
which drift into
coral
cracks
or land on
the ocean floor
develop
ing into females
哎我也问 any which
land on the
females pro
busses 啊是啊啊我想起来了这个
这个
看看过但是不知
道他长这样不能 make
them tell you 知道
有这种类型
的 who migrate to
her ut
iorist up to
twenty of
her sms can live
in her
body each
two hundred
thousand ti
mes
smaller
than
their mother and
she ha
s ultimate control
over
what
they do shes only
got
one request that
they have sex with
her
whenever
she wants 只看过科普书的没
有看过这
个就是图片的嗯带带带
这个视频的 female
banantia w
orms 口子需要吃 rather
than make males
come lo
oking
for them why not
create your own
when may you want
them
and
get what you want
whene
ver you wanted six
on
demand still to
come 基因
多样了
腺了怎么办不需要了 thanks 海
里都不需要
了雄只 mes 寄生寄
寄生在雌性体内吗小咪
感觉就是啊 right they
want t
o beat males
of their own game
and they take them
on every end of
the
way 谁发的刚刚那个东
西的总加词是 very
意思的都到那
去查一下行
我现在
去查一下
that test does
sterrun
field that he said
swag
ering males scrap
and f
ight
for food 嗯 for the
righ
t to maate
啊 in the thick of
this malse from
few ani
mals can mixed it
up li
ke the
hiuna 不 seeamas
mixed u
p as the hgha
late afternoon
没搜到啊没搜到啊啊这边没有 the
day
is hot the family
relax
还真适好
吃啊 the
head of the
clan swag is
passed bri
rustling
with testost rone
its
了为什
么我没搜到好吧等会
下播了再搜 with its
confide
nt well ll engaate
this
is one
in coook shal
killer bu
t this well hung
hunter
has a secret 啊我看到
你们发了我是 she 嗯是 is
the
queen of the swing
as a
huge member which
many miles would
be pro
ud to bear is in
fact l
ike
glitterrs a closer
look
at this family
reveals
theres not
a mile member site
猎狗的全
部成员都是战利 is a
sister hur
t 磁性吗它这种种群 these
female
s
are some of the
most ma
scular in the
world sniffing
reinforc
es family bonds
and the
res no smell on
earth
quite like this at
the
featal stage
female hin
ers ers come into
conta
ct
with high levels
of mal
e
hormones and it
causes
more
than hair on their
chest
these low slg
fitterise
s are even capable
of an erection 加强家
族情谊吗啊
不知道哎
他的那个 confusion 社会观
念会不太一样哦 dodging
with
fat 这谁 its
covered wit
h a thick effech
of
hair the that
on a males
testicles wi
th no external
vagina t
hat urinate mate
and gi
ve birth through
a cannee winning
down t
he centre this
shaft
males skull in the
back
ground subservient
三
方 and scared 哎
these fe
males are bigger
have y
ou and take them
all at
their
own game they
dominate
males in
almost every
situation
查的只
是一种颜色后缀
很多名字叫大 VV 的嗯 very
dis 就
是
形容是绿
色的你们这
个茶的话
像有一些
海兔啊然后还有一些
这个比如说狗尾巴草的种加词
就是
very DES 啊就是它是
绿色
的还有那种表示绿花
的有用 v dy flola
的然后有用 VEDS 的其
实就是形容颜色 once the
prey
has been blled
down fem
ales feed first
刚刚海虫
也
是绿的呀所以他就用这
个种家族绿叉什么来着
这个
字念
e 吗字念 tense
scrambles f
or food so when it
come
s to
sex its not
surprising
miles 我感觉这个攻略狗就是要瘦
一小
圈 timately they
pulled
the
ground to show
their su
bmission at the
first f
lash of bad
teeth 来 flee 嗯
if the response is
calm
er they creep
closer an
d risk a sniff to
see if the females
in s
eason 绿海阔鱼那个
很萌那个之前我查到
过图片很萌小小松不是啊小棕绿是一个物
种
啊小松
绿
整体是一个物种的 two
penesses a
re on a collision
crews
and its not easy
to
cock it up this is
the
one time
females can be the
hard
man strong
retractive
muscles let female
roll
has shafed out
like a
shirts leave
and create an
entrance
有十五次 he now has
her
whole attention
but fil
ling
in
the details
demands fro
m
at a narrow
patience an
d prots jbsen
pokes tha
t a
quick get away
after es
peculation if sex
was awkward ving
birth
birth a painus
really s
tretches the
point its a
nightmare
说两句吧
吧
别不
用看感觉做出什么
反应都不太对所以我们还是闭嘴
吧 and thats the
lucky
mothers after
twenty pe
rcent die
delivering th
eir first comes so
why
do the females
put themselves
through
this pain
many reasons have
been
suggested to
prevent
rape to confuse
mimic a
nd even prevent in
fant
asde
by males but
nobody kno
ws for
sure its one of
the gr
eat
mysteries of the
sexual
world 大伯笑不要
female choice
exist to
screen miles to
get the best
burm and
the best genam 谢谢同
水
的 hello 小松是署名吗绿是种大
字不小松
绿是中文正式
名因为他在中路
里面是这样的准
备署名和种
家词一定要放在拉丁舞的语境下才能
好并没有他没有任何人动物园的店长感谢
支
持现
在一样你再看
一局但看一直就该去吃饭了 these
mile
s on mely a
sperm bank in the
world
of
wild sex
evolutionary p
alel lies with
natural
spend 强烈建议
入选大逃杀的
食种已经养死了推荐看嗯爱你最
后一集了 it takes a
certain
type of mail
to achieve the
ultimate
fantasy sex on
town whenever with
whoe
ver however and
even wi
th
whatever entered
the do
minant mail but
theres
a price to pay
for all these
sex matcho males
must r
ule as potent
symbols o
f masculity they
must e
ndure exhausting
sexual
americans and
fight
hard with rival
males o
ver verrefething
from food and
females t
o territory and
still h
ave enough energy
to pr
oduce millions of
healt
hy sperm
throughout a l
ife that can
be grutal and
short tha
t 知道
讲什么话好呢
there are serious
strin
gs attached and
love 过
这些动物
在前面的几集里面都出现过
吧那个哦狮子猩然然
后那 almiles 都有出现过
we
all know that
relations
hips
between male and
female
may be complex
even di
fficult stretching
tolerance to the
limit
我这一屁股把后面重复变多了可
能他没有拍
那么多次属实 is remarky
staab
le 呃
可能也有可能是
就是好奇的让大家好奇的洞没有
那么多这两集跟前面是同一个
系列但是没
有做
中文的抑制 world of
spam
aneck these male
and fe
male sex cells
never co
mpete they were
togethe
r
this perfect
balance ex
ists because the
male p
roduces
lots of small
expendabl
e sex cells 口吃饭
what th
e female provides
far f
ewer
but much bigger
sounds
erex its the
perfect m
atch the problem
start
in trying to get
perman
ent together in
other words thanks
it
triggers the war
betwee
n the
sexes each gender
pursu
ing genetically
selfish
ends because a
natural
selection favs
only the
winner its at
this beh
avioral level
where cre
atures interact
through courtship
matin
g and conception
that
spectacular
conflicts b
reak out 没有那么多配音少了
点感觉这配
音
其实也挺
好玩的 such
confrontations
occur because
males and females
opera
te different
sexual str
ategies females
often h
ave the
opportunity to
get holdst
粉末的
one
mile allowing them
to e
xercise a kind of
quality control i
verho
o does the
fertinizing
and when but we
all know that
where sex
is concerned miles
alw
ays
like to come
呃 so the dominant
male
has evolved into a
vari
al sexy beast that
uses
group force the
蛮力 productive
rivals an
d achieve sexual
succes
s 主要好像动物也只能靠蛮丽了 to
take
whats right for
he ha
s the
stakes dont come
any h
igher in the world
of w
ild final sex
a male finds
himself un
der enormous
pressure t
o win the ultimate
cont
est survival
of his genes 可以制
造看到就是这个纪录片里
面有其他的这个除了蛮力之
外的竞争方式要
不然就是演技要不然就开眼开
眼算智力的那个那个蛇
的 dominance tends
to oc
cur
in
social groups
where fem
ales can regularly
made
with more than one
mil
e
孔雀算吗孔雀算纯展示 as
created
especitually
fierce spu
rn competition our
clos
est relative the
chimpa
nze their human
like
克雷夫谢谢姜公岩的哥们
儿双务老
师好刚刚教导主任
说都没去不许放这个好你好教导主任管不
到小松绿
老师拿到 my chin
is stronger than
three
grandmen
and they like to
hang out in group
these
morling 有没有
谈感情
的
动物 the forest life
三这个
纪录片里面好像没有很多我是真的感
情方面描述找一找 chins
live and
a man 更多的还是
对这个行为上 dominated
by fiercely
territal
miles 鸟不是吗他第一集的时候
有说其实鸟没有就是大家
想象的那么呃有感情有那个亲子
鉴定的出现对 home range
but
living smaller
groups t
hat are ruled
by strong mail
neighori
ng groups can
become a
lot
in violent
conflict as
rival
dominant
males mount
hostile rat
es this group is
the nu
cleus of the one
hundre
d strong community
谢谢嗯谢
谢港梦别人黑
天炸糖糕欢迎你你看纪录片也很好好
吵啊 but in chm
community 到底有
几个黑先生在叫 at the top
of
the hierarchy tree
is a
single solitary
chin i
m ela male aged
in his
mid twenties
请三十里 im sexally
hes r
eached his pick
the mos
t common strategy
for s
taying top chin is
inti
midation so the
earlies
t sign of a
challenge p
rovokes a fierce
and ch
arging to
满意这镜头也很动
感太晃动了 today from
a neighghbouring
group
the alpha male
ralliyes
his brotherhood
for co
ordinated cross
border
raid 越片风机 these
brutal
assaults can be
bloody
and even fatal
proving
just how
vividenttly th
e male
chm express ses
dominan
ce 那个闪来闪
去的剪
辑感觉在摸
什么凶案现场
一样 to us female
gins lo
ok like natures
batter
wives and the male
s id
ea
of a good time
looks mo
re like oppression
than
sex
these impressive
gestur
es are simply
non
verbal automatants
to the female that
sex
is what he wants
and th
eres no way out
of it
he also uses
satelliite
use
this frrentic
branch wa
ving indicates his
imme
diate state
of desire 那 but to
guar
antee he gets his
point
across
theres always the
brirustling
coat and his
impressive
erection 给女内衣哎呀这因为
嗯一因为
嗯嗯这应该是到到目前为止最
潮的一个
this emphasis on
the
visual signals as
evote
because chimpts
have g
ood eyesight and
see th
e world in color
perhap
s adapting
to life in
the three
dimensional f
orest meant
refining vi
sion to help
them hunt and
communica
te certainly
the sexual
language of
the champ has
focused on visual
clues
to reast
their sexual
arizon thi
s is not very
subtle to
us
its
really off
putting but to a
male c
hin with raging 喝什
么呢在喝什么我就 pick up
the sk
irt sexual
swelling get
s a
male chmp hot its
the
females
unmistaable way
of advertising her
urgent need for
sex chps pass on
male and female
rols th
rough a kind of
hands o
n
the sex education
this
open minded
approach ob
viously works
juveniles
really
like to watch
scrutiniz
ing
the acting closer
picki
ng up a few tips
includ
ing the art of
ejeculat
ion into ter 还有亲子教
育 unf
ortunately
for her not all
chin se
x is quite
as good as this
theres a downside
to t
he sexually
dominant lae this
is hi
s sister female
chins m
ay be
incredibly
permiscuous
but even they draw
the
line at brothers
unfort
unately 来往朝天
he appears to
arouse to
can and
after beating her
into
submission
不试试 i
have thanks and
theres
more to come its
not
just on the family
leve
l that
chmps are sexually
aggr
essive the batroom
cont
inues inside the
female
chin shes been
penetra
ted by other males
and
their
sperm is now
running a
microscopic act
race th
is
is where things
really
begin to get
aggressive
as the tunnel of
love is
transformed into a
back
home around this
is th
e 不分无 this 闪闪光三 d
建模
they support the
office
吧 so that the
whole ej
culate works
like a
micromotherhoook
fighting its way
to the end 嗯 the
sexual
role
for these
chemicazys b
urm is not to
create li
fe but to block
the opp
osition 唉
不过这个
这个说法好
像有在其他的生物书里面就是
看到
过唉 we take a long
hard
look the
generitalso so
me some of nature
s sma
llest sexy beasts
and t
he exhausting sex
life
我的
live 导航 while some
spen
d become sexual
weapons
the painus that
ultima
te symbol of my
ulvoril
ity can be
just as effective
in th
e right hands
natures
most impressive
genotar
ia generally
belong to
the smaller life
forms
刚
刚在揉一 it call 了 the
mark
et in the
femidical pae
ce 嗯送物 female
promosccurity is
many m
iles greatest
sphere it
s
not just pride
thats
its stake here it
s li
fe and that 下次就把
摄像头关
了 put apart from a
nopp
ilizing
cess to his mate
there
are a
few ways for a
mile to
eliminate
the competition 地点
也要说一会
儿再滴眼药水吧现在还好现在
只是有点痛痛的
males will do
virtually
anything to
subvert co
ntrol
female choice bed
bugs
clearly
have the same
unpleasan
t habits as most
paracitic blood
suckers
inflating like
bloody
balloons
on the
flash 这个
很坏吸血的都是坏
的哦 mister their
rankind
最讨厌
的就是这
种蚊子啊然后
什么跳蚤啊还有这
个
臭虫之类
的 shes got a
perfectly
good
set of such such
organs
in other words a
fully functioning
genit
al
trend but hes nt
afte
r
something a little
more
unusual 看到蚊子一定要
打死 hes in
possession o
f yet
another awesome
peanuts
which he ells
like a sod 你问小松为什么
虫子都喜欢 that box sex
他咬我他
就他就不喜欢他不行有
人能平等的爱所有的虫包括蚊子
吗你做到到
啊虫虫才屁虫的话是不是被咬了之
后
一定要去医院啊它会传播一
些病毒之类
的
然后很容易发烧 by
ejaculating
his sperm directly
into
the females
bloodstrea
m guarantees one
hundre
d percent that he
ll be
the one to
fertilize erix 他为
头感觉
还可
以可以看我们咬
你时后感受包慢
慢变大有一天
the female backbag
has
a pad
of tissue in her 有
一些不太好
的倾向呢 which helps
repair
the damage caused
by be
ing stabbed in a
stomac
h with a
shop pailance to
make t
his
method of
insemination
work the female
bedbog
has also evolved
this 臭虫在北方有吗不
知道我现
在臭虫很
少 circulates
through he
r bund stream it
become
s lodged in this
plant
i
stoled until she
gets h
er next blood meal
when
shall be ready to
produ
ce a batch of eggs
南方的不
要因为
小时候话还有什么狮子啊臭
虫之类的
现在都没有了跳蚤都没见过跳蚤现在跳
蚤挺多的 send directly
into
the
bloodstream sperm
canno
t be scooped out
its
unstoppable life
can al
so be dramatic for
my old bet 影
翅虫听说很恐怖银
翅虫有
几个就是有毒的鼠要注意
一下如果在家里发
现了一定要注意杀虫那
个那个粘到人会很肿肿的他的那
种感位 and once
hes ejeculated
his spe
rn was slowly but
very
surely
migrate all the
way to
the smaller males
verde
deference
or spend out so
when th
e trauw was
over and 有的影之
手很帅有
几个有几个就是长得个体很大
的食物
不是肥 one mile
forcing an
other to carry out
the ture of of
insiinat
ion 怎么还要抢后
方呢 but theres a
lot more to being
a dom
inant male than
just ha
ving a fancy
peds what about
fathhoo
d and fulfilling a
real
pavental role for
this
kind of thing
we need to scale
up to
the larger more
conspic
uous miles
of the animal
world you
probably dont
get much
more males than
this 昨天
晚上看见一个屁股是橙黑色我
记得那个黑色和橙
色条纹
的那个隐视虫都是有毒的一巴
拉斯拉拉斯拉警惕一下吧拿拿
纸捏死它 this has to
be the
ultimate
testing ground for
the
uber mile lions
are at
the top of many
superle
agues a ed
predator big
gest cat the
enemies an
d they
have an enormous
sexual
appetite over one
hund
red and fifty
times 其实小
时候对
于狮狮子啊这种就是草原动
物的了解大部
分都来自于动画片动画
片演什么样就记得是什
么样 this predigious
sexu
al
appetite is hard
wide i
nto the
line you know a
book th
eir clinical
sinks many iex 除了
狮子王还有别
的动画片也会有狮
子争关的 relentless or
most
mechanical nonstop
calp
ulation is her
fuone it
takes a lot
of sex
to get a lion as
pregna
nt were talking
vigoro
us stimulation 小时
候对动物的
理解全部来自于什物我们 make
it three first
year it
requires mum and
dad to
have had sex
嗯谢谢港猛捏死
影吃虫毒液会流出来吧嗯是
这样的就是拿
个纸捏死
perhaps this is
the
answer 多包几层纸吧
famous de
line theres a
great de
alate sake he
needs to perform
well t
he pride
rely on him to
sign the
next generation
dissurpride
already has
a dozen adult
females
and suppordinment
males
with several young
com
es all living
under
the rule of their
power
ful pride chief a
domin
ant a yerold mail
life
is looking
pretty good 没小狮子可爱
呢小狮子玩尾巴可爱你 but
theres
trouble brewing
this is
a
lone maradding
mail he
has no pride of
his own
and at six years
old 其实有的时候看
这种动物都不太
会换算他们的年龄就
是具体嗯几岁是成年然后几岁是
壮年就不同的动物会不太一样我也记不太
清 the
res only one real
thre
at to
an
adult mail il line
they
have no natural
enemie
s just at the
males warnings
through
sentenence ed and
usually worked to
pek 老
的还明星高我的
可以看看面向 when things
do
escalate into full
conflict 不
研究
这个基本都算不过来对呀就是不
同动物的区别太大了蟑螂几
岁是成年你问问蟑螂诶张老
师宽虫昆虫一般不是算那
个一零二零若虫重重吗好今天怎么假了
there
s
nearly five
hundred keo
os of my
aggression in
conflict 看
牙齿最靠怕了我
也不
张嘴一样对
finally the old
male ba
cks down leaving
the territory
never to
return his pride
has
taken a knock but
hes
left alive 发现
尸体中他有的时候剪的就很
像尸体发
现啊凶案现场还有那个闪来闪去的 to
come
the new ruling
male car
ries out the
horodian
lalaughter of
the prize youngest
come
s 哎这
一
部分也是小时时
看书的时候见过植物
有
年龄龄一
一说吗有啊你比
如说嗯果在
在小时候之前
结果
结结 even killed 好
有什么就是
反正五六年吧五六年梨
树和不会开不会不会结果子的
这样的说法桃树李树和
杏树吗打零还有你 killing
these
young coes purges
the prime of the
old mi
les bloodline
小松为什么说小松位
是人哎呀小松
林是什么 was my
only escape death
by le
aving the pride
after the takeover
谢谢
despite the HSSR
mainin
g members have all
the
benefits they
enjoy bef
ore 一醒来就进
直播间看星星的雷霆行为清醒才意
识到看到了什么
今天就要看这个赶紧看完
下次就不放这
么雷霆的了 by killing
the cu
bs of the
old mail the new
male h
as pulled a
remarkable
biological tricger
with
no succling cubs
left
the females will
become
fertiand again 下次
看什么还没想好下次给我看点看点
海洋的吧 and we all
know wh
at that means 不
雷体
我不看 its a good
job he
didnt exhaust
themmsel
f taking
over the pride
this lin
e has now
got three very
honey lo
nesses
to
satisfy and for
the nex
t few days hes
going t
o be having sex
every t
en ten to fifteen
minut
es 拿一层待
衣
rain or shine 想看海洋
生物这种这样就觉得海洋
生物有很多很多
好玩的海洋生物一
般
都
长得比较变
态 but its not all
wine
and roses for her
像那
个安康鱼
都不能炸红酒啊 so that it
hurt
s so when he
withdraws
水母
母又是外的水母母那个贝贝那又是另
外的之
前是不是还有那种就是嗯榜单说什
么
海洋里面最毒的是谁的那种榜单
sesetual action to
conc
eive she also
needs exa
ctly the right
kind of
stimulaation 哦
绿萝和那个什么水母香水母吗
比较比较毒啊啊你 the pain
也
罢 the miles
heavily bou
ght painus 野榜
也爱看男神 ultimately
the se
xual extravagance
of lions must be
benefi
cial and its
quite
likely of the
males are
getting far more
out th
is situation 三貌
水母严格来
说不算水母
啊 perhaps the more
ener
getically the
females a
re stimulated
the less likely
they ar
e to start playing
away
which means
the better lover
you ar
e the
more likely you
are to
father cub 蓝环章鱼啊风
貌水
母不是
那个由那个水系集合
体组成的吗我应该没记错吧它繁殖方式是
在就是在有
风暴的时
候飞到飘到海面
上然后等
那个风暴把它打碎了然后
它那个每一个小块
的水吸然后就是重新长成一个新
的僧茂水母他那
个繁殖也很好玩 infantasde
is
just another
particular
ly violent form of
sperm competition
becau
se it increases
the
killers
reproductive su
ccess and his
chances o
f thering off
spring
水系和
水母不都
是青刀洞吗但是你
从这个繁殖方式就很明显
不太一样啊 like
that the 能不能把它划
到一类吗
the most
competitives 软
模子 happening
species
看出来素材复用了
又在黑色刚刚已经演过一轮黑猩鼠没事
socia
l stability leads
to di
fferent
sexual strategies
and 你
最后一集都
没有出出呀啊 take the
silver
banangorilla 另一种大猩
猩怎么能卖
哦 but
equipped with just
a
five centimeter
penis 大
猩猩 best 的 goals it
s on
e of our
fammilliastere
otypes
the overpumped
muscle m
an
huge mp 哎剩两种
chest but for the
male
gorilla having a
tiny f
elous actually
make sen
se despite what we
see
as his shortcomes
this
silver back
gororilla i
s sexally speaking
very
lucky hes in
total control of
all
these females hes
the
only one who gets
to
have
sex with them and
every
other gurl around
here
obease him 而且
这个看起来没有
刚刚的那个
那么凶那个没有黑猩猩那么
凶
but youd be a
fool to
try and
pinch one of his
wives
啊我说咋了 but why
does such
an
icon of male
dominance
and physical
strength
end up with a
panas
around the size of
a hu
man thun 这
不就是黑心这个不是说
是银背大猩猩吧肯
定是两个 the fact is
gorillas are
simply mat
ching their supply
这的这么的 he can
afford to
economize on sperm
and
production
operators be
cause he rules an
incre
dibly
stable social
group 肚子
females along
to his oriam the
cost o
f my osperm
production
is 这个 compared to
the f
emale leg but that
does
nt mean its
entirely
trivial it still
requir
es valuable
physical an
d biological
resources
to keep a
good supply on tap
and
any male that can
econo
mize on his sexual
appperators on
spend pe
nis and testicles
will
have plenty of
energy l
eft for
building large
muscles
underpending the
maalgo
rilla s dominance
over
the group is
a strong
richalized soc
ial system a kind
of on
e life mafia one
silver
back it
lives in
the next and ded
family
your females and
their
rock spring and in
man
y cases a number
of clo
sely
related 那就没有 such
stabi
lity leaves the
superba
nk to pursue his
main g
oal to mate with
as
many females
as possible to
increase
his chances of
reprodu
ctive success 好像
没有注意过这个猩猩类的物都在哪里呢你
平时在动
物园见到的其实也是猴子
比较
多 but he probably
has 很
少
了解到星猩相关的 and
gorilla se
x tryas are
strong on the
fringes
of many green 非洲吗非
洲国 ar
e their
mating chances are
next
and nothing 太热带了
and i
t seems such
outcast males 然后鸿
毛相香之外基
本
都在非洲
show society es
where o
mominant
males defend their
heri
nes of females
however
while the silver
back c
an depend on
the strong ritul
of gorililas
society to
keep control
there are some
harrees
es where dominant
males
really output
through t
heir paces 小聪明不是老师
啊小聪明只
是爱
只是爱看纪录片而已不代表什么都会啊
the myeleelephants
eal
isnt everyones
idea o
f the perfect
partner
哦你怎么是你怎
么是一潘 his fat at
leleps around
around fo
rforces
mmself from
females and
they dont look
like t
he most caring
parents
however the male
elepha
nt seal it does
managed
to perform a
crucial
parental role that
if p
rotection the
beach can be a
dangerou
s place for a
vulnerabl
e young elephant
seal
especially when
grogroe
n ts are
having sex BGM
又来了 once a year
elephan
cials turn up on
this
speech to have a
wild m
ating party these
bulls
are full of
pentups 是蓝
了之一 and its about
to g
et released they
hold themselves
onto th
e beaches long
before t
he females are due
to a
rrive 还
不要真的分担哦
males must first
establ
ish territories
which w
ork like
bachelhella ad
s to attract
females th
ese alpha mios or
beach
masters not the
bigges
t the wall and as
the
beach begins to
fill up
with perspective
blobe
r lovers decent
territo
ries base becomes
scarc
e
antiststosterrow
levels
begin to 可用的地盘越来越少
就刚刚那个高一
点的嗯摄
像头就是看到海滩上全
都是 elephancy bulls
are
also
bebeassed real
heavy we
ights
over three
thousand keo
os of
aggressive 三千公斤中这个
哎等一下哎
出多少公斤 lined with
over s
ix hundred kekilos
of b
lubber and that
massive
head that nearly
fifty
hilos
what is the same
out wh
ich keeps
everything mo
ving just about 毒死
硬死 wa
y twice as much
as females the
massive
difference has
been sha
ped 世界
strategy the size
of th
e female is
determined
purely
by natural
election in
other words
environment
al adaptations
that hav
e helped them eat
more
grow faster
戴点水 what the males
tryi
ng to seek have
been ho
ned to
affection by
mixture of
necorres 看
着其实
跟那个什么海
报一样的就想
着比海大大一点的
粉刺哟他这也太大了 just
se matter its his
stra
tegy success even
as
the
females make their
each
head davies the
males
are still bilk y
as the
y compete fiercely
for territory
those wit
h established
beach spa
ce must keep it
protect
ed against vival
males on the
loocounter
for a prime sport
this period of
challeng
e and
counterchallenge
is a critical part
deve
lopment see your
coacht
ion 谢
谢你们你太日太阳
正常升起的的光棒能骗
下
小鸠吗只吃中药等一下我等会儿再去喊他
fema
les 都
会下播了就给他发消
息
你是个归即间归一的钢管 about
but e
ach female is
looking for more
than s
afe sex from her
protec
tor theres an
even mor
e
urgent requirement
she
is about to give
birth
before they have
sex the females
will ha
ve last year his
pumps
and they need a
male ar
ound
to make sure they
re le
ft 真
配 ace so hes
really
on a promise by
oversee
ing mother
and pump through
birth
and succling you
ll kee
p her around long
enoug
h to have
thanks her
breeding str
ategy is called
delayed
in
plantation the
fertiliz
ed dag doesnt
implant and begin
to de
velop until the
timing
is right for the
featur
es to
be bomb just
before the
next mating season
这个策略
在刚刚为
什么
动物里面也
有 it goes and
ensuring
most babies are
born wi
th an a few
weeks of each
other the
following year
females
come back into
heat ni
neteen
days after giving
birth
and will be
receptive
不知道
我 four days and it
s on
ly then that the
male
s approacher for
things
北极熊吗
应该二十百这种被
季节影响很大的谢谢星光香水母的糖宝香
水母比较
懂香水母比
较毒我是
记得它应该是水母里面最毒
的你在水里面中间有
一个橙色的然后那个图变
不一样
的忘记具体是哪一种
了
protecting and
servicin
g
these arrooms
spreadad
the mye elephants
cial
pretty thin its a
the
the protection for
weeks on end
during whi
ch theyll stop
eating
just to try and
king co
ntrol
of their mating
opportu
nities this sexual
stra
tegy is called
female d
efence polligny 我
感觉他们移动
起来就
是好辛苦啊这么这么沉一个然
后然后还有平率 a very
tough an
d physically
demanding life
requirin
g massive energy
invest
ment 香水我也不是真事有没有关于
水
母的纪录片啊 they may be
big
and
strong but my
elephant seals
live con
siderably
shorter than
females el
ephcies are
extreme as
far as mammals are
conc
erned their
mating strategy
make so
me males far
more successful
than ot
hers
purely because of
their size and
strength
蓝色星我应该有蓝色星球
没有专门开 councils
have the kind of
physic
al presence to be
a bea
ch master so
我去找一找 and as a
conseque
nce some
opportunistic
miles developed
an ingeneous
alternativ
e strategy to
sexual
success despite
the emp
hasis here on size
and
strength theres
still some room
for the
little
guy to
get lucky these
smaller
miles im out
along th
e edge of the
rukky and
try to make when
the hu
rry master is
asleep wi
ll busy 下一步看
什么还没想好我去
找
一下去检索一下有没
有好玩的 while sexual
selec
tion for the
elephancy
is intense enough
to cr
eate a massive
differen
ce in male female
size
such extremes can
also
create other
strategies
to realize less on
bro
om 如今凑热来了 not
surprisin
gly
sneeky miles 那古生感兴
趣吗小时候
爱看古生
物现在
没那么爱看 whats nt
it for
them well i do out
little time an
lephant to growing
large enough to
fight f
or a territory and
don
t invest hardenned
valu
able energy
parental ca
t
instead of
building mus
cle tables
spam and the cost
of sp
erm is not
triviealed b
y
effectively
parasitizin
g the dominant and
terr
itorial males they
also
pass on the
sneaker ge
ne to future
generation
s in some species
the s
neaker
mile can become as
succ
essful as his
dominant
pears 制豆来了是吗啊
after the break
wild se
x reveals why
despite h
is rivado a mattro
me
is outnumbered and
out
cast by a group of
fema
les
there is no single
sexu
al strategy but 这玩
意儿 depends large 还
有 wha
t you rival is
doing 哇
还有插入的 sex
strategies or
a bit like a game
of
paper scissors
stone no
thing works every
time
but the snaker
mail has even
managed t
o undermine the
huge
physical presence
of th
e beach master 广告闪
了一秒也不
一
定是广告吧咱就
插插入了一小片段无关的 in a
few sp
ecies
the sneaker may
have th
e most
effective sexual
strate
gy of all the
jelarada abooon
social
system was once
describ
ed as one me a
group
they live in large
troo
ps hundreds
of individuals
together
occupying the high
gra
sslands of
ethoppia
这部的感觉完全是就
是很小很小的时候看的那种几乎漂亮防撞
车或者
规避版觉的查查有
可能
females that
associate
with
one dominant male
or is
not what it seems
the
dominant
male looks like a
hurri
ant male
and roughly twice
the
size of the female
and
scorting a large
set of
k nine unty for
fighti
ng and finishes
off the
look with a
spectacular
flowing me hes an
ani
mal advertising
his abi
lity to inflict
terrible 到到后了呢这应该就
最后一个动
物了吧马
上就结束了没
办法为什
么爸爸不要 the
male ylada does a
lot o
f fighting
engaging in
fierce battles
with riv
al mile 为什
么它的毛很长看起来就相比较起来要干净
一点什么这也顺滑也很干净看起来
很蓬松哦静静那
个小的就
没有那么蓬松了成
年呢看起来比较蓬
松 research is
shown but
not all
miles take the
matcho a
pproach
就
好 reing leadership
野人
给他用户发死好搞笑 instead
some
establish
long term
relationships
with just one
or two
females this might
look
like
second best and
the onl
y option for a
loser bu
t because these
males n
ever engage in
violent
fights 带类子龙的 so a
submi
ssive strategy
could actually
mean
greater
reproductive su
ccess throughout a
peac
eful knife as
filateral
balance neither
male s
trategy excludes
the ot
her in
fact
loud luders is
both but that
something
都蛮要
知道的采取两种措施想打架的可
以打架不想打
架了用不想打架
的过法我们的 facebit
theres
a
simple contract
between
the male jelada
and
his harin for as
long a
s hes physically
impressive and
supports his hree
inclu
ding
protecting the
young he
has exclusive
mating r
ights but the
jilara ma
y not be in total
control of his
destiny
because as soon
as the female 这画质糊
到
一旦远景了就是它的毛的边缘
都有点融
化掉了 when a female
is re
ady for sex a ring
of r
ed beeding
developed on
the naked patch of
her
chest 唉什么部分
visibly
swells attracting
the m
iles
at this time these
fema
les are
the true sexual
leaders
of this group
because
they may choose to
supp
ort or oppose a
dominan
t mill 不行不行镜头有点太晃动
我就打下去
who wins
the contest for
control
of the trip the
female
s can chase any
unwanted myalloout
of h
is own territory
by a c
ombine
show of physically
那个
狒狒的颜色和背景有点
融为一体 so
despite the male
s
larger size and
greater
strength its the
gala
da a females
that have the
ultimate
say in his
reproduct
to
success 动态快了
可能之前的那个拍摄水平没
有现在高吧排了
好久才
潜出来那点都有 the
evolutional
alalnanative 啊到最后了
how
many 中前的部分
已经结束了 say from the
high cost
conventional
or mkiismo the
fact is
while most females
amon
g most species
will hav
e
thanks
successfully rep
roduced the
majority of
miles 不
用闹野外摄有没有
很难不就是拍野生动物要更难吧
in human terms the
fema
les of most
species are
shameless
那算了
and wanting and
most lu
stful males 还有
十分钟间 KPI 但是晚上还有晚上还
有
这
个直播来的个 an
evolution 晚上还
要打游戏呀 weve seen
that m
ales compete
formates s
ometimes volently
and that the
winners of
these bouts seem
to th
en have complete
contro
l of
the mating process
but
the stereotypes of
pass
ive female and
aggressi
ve 谢谢谢黄鼠 mmolos
for charts part of
the
story
在卷
出一边拍
行刀处一边喂蚊子吸
血虫确实好烦可以安慰一下吧天
哪宝宝大夏天
的在景区拍行道树吗好辛苦
啊 highly
competitive an
imals 注意带驱蚊水 only
evolu
tion of wild
thanks 一哎好
听哈哈这个好看的
这个好看
的下次下次再
找一个新的纪录片来看吧大
家然后再张回来 ok
给这个收个尾今天的直播
就到这里结束再见了所有的动物之恋
的六级已经完了
感觉不如前四集好看确实后面
就
是策略上面都比较重复了还
是前四级前四集是精华我们小小谢一下礼
物就可以
撤离啦就下
下一次唉晚上那
个我还在想
晚上的这个联动到底
要怎么办呢挠头中联动加记录片好之后四
级
后两集是拼上去的呃不是他这个中文
是四级但是看了一下后
两集英文的片头很明显跟前面四级
是连着的
老大我们家能火一局吗不一定啊你现在你
现在说这个一切都
是未知哦谢谢 BB 五一二
二八三五
零八一三二星光铃铛谢谢米
翰鼓掌谢谢
全妹的
鼓鼓掌谢
是个萨姆的豆腐三
灯牌谢谢苹果三
爷的鼓
鼓掌谢谢关心动物
神娘糖的捏捏小脸谢谢闪光落
伊的金
光铃铛谢谢呃屌丝挖
到呃粉
丝安灯卡一
谢白拜大王爱心抱
枕和棉花糖谢谢鸽子整薯条的人气票谢谢
黄
鱼薯条的鼓掌谢谢四
小时后提莫记
的鼓鼓
掌谢谢香菜医生致点鼓鼓掌谢谢你家哎呀
礼物谢谢谢小可
今天吃
什么都鼓鼓掌就这样吧因为那个呃
试了一下如果如果画质开的高的话这个电
脑会有一点
火热所以到时候小
松绿
这边的这个画质肯定是有一些搞笑
的谢谢一条
咸鱼空
闲的说唱虚假
的绿卡子
虚无
电
台更回点播回真正的绿卡血压游戏回纪录
片
行刀术游戏会确实游戏会确实大
家能看进趣游戏真
是太太不容易了谢
谢小聪明妹 supad 今天只要不
是每局
都第一个死就算胜利不一定啊真不一
定啊我感觉总会有有人比
小棕绿死得到吧谢谢痴香禅道小们准备听
天
堂组相声了就
是就会有点担心这
个晚上没有话说啊真的真的不一定有
相声听很担心谢谢库
瓦特罗巴基娜的港光对了致命公司里面有
小棕榈最
爱的大蜘蛛大蜘蛛吗期待一下没
看谢谢都能送的嗯佛山灯牌谢谢
ESCON 意
外的鼓掌谢一凤鼓掌
谢谢正逢夏末秋凉的
鼓掌谢谢大家有大爆脸虫跟那个
report 的
那个
抱脸图一样吗这真要
抓紧时间
去搜一下攻略了谢谢 OCW 的比心谢
谢大家比那
个吓人我们昨天又遇到那个就是会会炸掉
的那个粘
粘液嘛就是它爆
炸了之后会喷那到处
都是粘液的那个挺吓人的还
有装队友的伟人哦他们昨
天还遇到什么假门了是吗就是那
个门是假的然后你会被被
吃掉什么的什么墨的不知道到啊我我这是
纯粹的跟着
那个那个墨的安装然
后一个一个装到最后其实不
太清楚自己装了什么
东西谢
谢驰军老
飞兽的舰掌剑感
谢支持真感谢支持伟
人木的能粘
增加小红
率的
参与
感不知道哎有复活摸的吗不知道不知道
一个都一
个都没注意根本不清
楚什么谢谢洛洛洛西的高们
飞船上有个机器是看其
他人的大大方方练口条解说看看呢看看呢
我也是能模
仿的小
峰律
师啊我要去看我要去看解
说了有新电脑之
后多玩就好了就不太接触这种多人联动游
戏啊确实是
没怎么跟人玩过游戏啊就这个跟自己玩儿
不太
一样多联动好吗那不
一定能啊不一定
能啊这打玩两次看看一下这个
联动的效效果吧自己
玩就会玩吗
自己玩的话没有一种会拖累其他人的
负罪感啊然后派
对游戏如果大他说派对游戏的
话其实一个都没有玩过第一个玩的派对游
戏
是那天联动的 report 联动爬
塔享受一
下联动爬塔就不一定了联动爬塔
可能
就是互互相攻击了有找几个知名公司的视
频你一起
看看好吗
自自己偷
偷看自己
偷
偷看自己偷
偷看先谢派大星吹雪的
港猛 XSL 会像
大前辈一样被吓哭吗会被吓
到但是一
般小棕绿的话不会被吓哭吧八画不能说死
我们后面
加个八就避免真的出现这种情况了唉
小苏莉也不玩
恐怖游戏会
被那个詹姆
scare 吓到他出现的时候会会下愣
会下愣住没
有尖叫的部分就
已经被吓吓愣住了还好没
那么吓人吗没那么吓
人就好对虫子进
行研究能看虫子长什么样
子看看晚上是什么样子的没有蟑螂吓
人怎么样蟑螂僵尸 gear 还
是很吓人的然后小聪明应该会把自己这边
的音量
稍微调整小一点避免避免太吵闹捡垃圾然
后
有小怪懂了懂了懂了我们今天下我的直播
就先这样吧
晚上的联
动的
时候再见了好吗好嘛好
嘛好嘛平时
就已经很小声了那就保持现在这个好好吗
超哥给晚上
还有晚上还
有晚上还不知
道晚上还不知道要玩到几点呢好吧拜拜
拜拜晚上再见吧是
不是是是